

Ismail Aabrar

• Home: Munir Chowdhury Bhaban, Flat-A5, Fuller Road, Dhaka University Campus, 1000, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Email: <u>iaabrar16@gmail.com</u> **\ Phone:** (+880) 1786492826

Website: https://iaabrar16.github.io/iaabrar.com/

Whatsapp Messenger: https://wa.me/+8801786492826

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/iaabrar/

Gender: Male **Date of birth:** 16/12/1999 **Nationality:** Bangladeshi

ABOUT ME

I am a university student at United International University, specializing in CSE. Beyond my academic pursuits, I find joy in playing futsal, where I hone my physical and mental abilities while fostering teamwork. I also enjoy driving, which provides me with a sense of freedom and adventure. By striking a balance between my hobbies and studies, I lead a fulfilling life and am poised to succeed in both my personal and professional endeavors.

WORK EXPERIENCE

[09/2021 - 04/2022]

Intern

Global Digital Solutions https://higlobaldigitalsol.wixsite.com/website

City: Dhaka

Country: Bangladesh

Tasks -

- · Lead Generation.
- Lead Analysis.
- · Project Management.
- · Mobile App Testing.
- · Website Testing.
- · Canva.
- · Take interviews for new interns.
- Search for Client.
- UI Design.
- SEO

[09/2021 - 03/2022] **Project Leader**

Upscribbr

City: Minnesota

Country: United States

Tasks -

- Lead Generation.
- · Lead Analysis.
- Project Management.
- · Mobile App Testing.
- · Website Testing.
- UI Design.
- SEO

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[01/2020 - Current]

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering

United International University https://www.uiu.ac.bd/

Address: Madani Avenue, 1212, Dhaka, Bangladesh

[06/2017 - 07/2019] Higher Secondary Certificate Examination

King's College https://kingscollege.edu.bd/

Address: House#25, Road#5, Uttara, Sector-7, 1230, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Final grade: GPA 4.08 out of 5.00

[01/2015 - 05/2017]

Secondary School Certificate Examination

Winsome School & College https://cambrian.edu.bd/winsome/index.html

Address: House# 6-7/A, Block-B, Lalmatia., 1205, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Final grade: GPA 5.00 out of 5.00

PROJECTS

Projects

- 1. Build a Football Game using JavaFX and SceneBuilder for the Advanced Object Oriented Programming Laboratory.
- 2. Build Social Media using PHP, MySql, and Bootstrap for Database Management Systems Laboratory.
- 3. Build School Management using Aurdino with Hardware for Electronics Laboratory.
- 4. Build a simple Converter using Java Swing for Object Oriented Programming Laboratory.

SKILL DEVELOPMENT **COURSES**

HTML5, CSS3 & Bootstrap 4 For Web Development

- HTML Tags, Forms, Media, APIs.
- CSS Basic Components and CSS Responsive.
- Bootstrap 4 and Its Components and Project Using Bootstrap.

Link: https://bohubrihi.com/courses/html5-css3-and-bootstrap-4

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Bengali

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B1 READING B1 WRITING B1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B1 SPOKEN INTERACTION B1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Java | HTML | CSS | PHP | MySQL | JavaScript | C | JavaFX | Scene Builder | Assembly | Python | Microsoft Office Suite